[

    {
        "question": "Pair this please 1",
        "answers": [ "book", "jumper", "pencil", "car", "hat", "cake", "socks" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "könyv", "pullóver", "ceruza", "autó", "sapka", "sütemény", "zokni" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45
    },
    {
        "question": "Pair this please 2",
        "answers": [ "pen", "bag", "toothbrush", "T-Shirt", "hairbrush", "guitar", "baloon" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "toll", "táska", "fogkefe", "póló", "hajkefe", "gitár", "lufi" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45

    },
    {
        "question": "Pair this please 3",
        "answers": [ "towel", "pencilcase", "dog", "train", "shoes", "cat", "Dad", "Mum" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "törölköző", "tolltartó", "kutya", "vonat", "cipők", "macska", "apa", "anya" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45

    },
    {
        "question": "Pair this please 4",
        "answers": [ "chair", "table", "pen", "teacher", "book", "clock", "loud", "quiet" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "szék", "asztal", "toll", "tanár", "könyv", "óra", "hangos", "csendes" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45
    },
    {
        "question": "Pair colors",
        "answers": [ "red", "orange", "blue", "pink", "yellow", "green", "black" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "piros", "narancssárga", "kék", "rózsaszín", "sárga", "zöld", "fekete" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45

    },
    {
        "question": "Pair this please 6",
        "answers": [ "listen", "fish", "cheese", "yoghurt", "bread", "rice", "see" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "hallgat", "hal", "sajt", "joghurt", "kenyér", "rizs", "lát" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45

    },
    {
        "question": "Pair this please 7",
        "answers": [ "tiger", "monkey", "zebra", "crocodile", "lion", "run", "climb trees" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "tigris", "majom", "zebra", "krokodil", "oroszlán", "fut", "fára mászik" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45

    },
    {
        "question": "Pair this please 8",
        "answers": [ "ice cream", "Goodbyev !", "look", "cow", "milk", "fly", "sunhat", "pasta" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "jégkrém", "Viszont látásra !", "nézd", "tehén", "tej", "repül", "kalap", "tészta" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 60

    },
    {
        "question": "Pair this please 9",
        "answers": [ "butter",  "brown", "mouth", "blond", "soup", "and", "thank you", "face" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "vaj",  "barna", "száj", "szőke", "leves", "és", "közönöm", "arc" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45

    },
    {
        "question": "Pair this please 10",
        "answers": [ "kitchen", "bedroom", "bathroom", "sitting room", "hall", "garden", "trainers", "dress" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "konyha", "hálószoba", "fürdőszoba", "nappali", "előszoba", "kert", "tornacipő", "ruha" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 60

    },
    {
        "question": "Pair colors 2",
        "answers": [ "white", "blond", "brown", "pink", "yellow", "green", "black" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "fehér", "szőke", "barna", "rózsaszín", "sárga", "zöld", "fekete" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45

    }

]